{
    "subject": "Blanche_I_of_Navarre",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "John_II_of_Aragon",
    "human_readable": "Blanche I of Navarre is married to John II of Aragon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9338846802711487,
            "question": "Who was Blanche I of Navarre married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9086527824401855,
            "question": "Who is John II of Aragon married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8728501200675964,
            "question": "Which king was married to Blanche I of Navarre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8350896239280701,
            "question": "Who is John II of Aragon's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8127246499061584,
            "question": "Name the queen who was married to John II of Aragon."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7990062832832336,
            "question": "Was Blanche I of Navarre married to a king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6168190836906433,
            "question": "To whom did Blanche I of Navarre become betrothed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4694298803806305,
            "question": "What was the name of John II's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45797643065452576,
            "question": "What is the name of John II's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31823933124542236,
            "question": "What royal family did Blanche I belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Blanche I of Navarre is married to John II of Aragon.",
            "html": "yago_11210_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of John II's wife?",
            "html": "yago_11210_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of John II's wife?",
            "html": "yago_11210_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom did Blanche I of Navarre become betrothed?",
            "html": "yago_11210_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11210_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11210_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11210_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11210_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11210_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11210_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11210_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11210_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11210_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11210_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that Queen Blanche I of Navarre was a wife, but they do not specify who her husband was. However, later on, it is mentioned that John II of Aragon (who married Queen Blanche I) was the father of Blanche II of Navarre, and that Blanche II's mother was also named Blanche I, implying that she is a different person from the initial Blanche I.\n\nTherefore, based on this information, there are actually two different women with the name Blanche I of Navarre in these documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Blanche I of Navarre is married to John II of Aragon.\" Specifically, it mentions that John II of Aragon was the husband of Queen Blanche I of Navarre and that he ruled as King of Navarre alongside her."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "John II of Aragon is married to Blanche I of Navarre's daughter, Queen Blanche II of Navarre.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}